http://www.malariavaccine.org/privacy-policy

Evaluation technologies
AccessGlobal policy and regulatory pathwaysRegulatory decisions and prequalifications
Policy
Preparing for malaria vaccine decisionsThe decision-making framework tool for malaria vaccines
Propose a project
About usOur leadership teamDonorsContact usMalaria and vaccinesNeed for a vaccineRTS,SMalaria vaccine roadmapNext-generation vaccinesPreventing transmissionPreventing infectionVaccine developmentOur research and development strategyLife cycle of the malaria parasitePreferred product characteristicsEvaluation technologiesAccessGlobal policy and regulatory pathwaysPreparing for malaria vaccine decisionsFinancingProjectsSearch vaccine projectsEvaluation technology projectsMVI PortfolioPast projectsResourcesSearch all resourcesFact sheetsJournal articlesPresentationsVideosReportsNews and eventsPress releasesPerspectivesMalaria vaccine newsEventsWork with usRFPsAdvocacyMalaria Vaccine Advocacy FellowshipPast advocacy fellowsTools for advocatesPropose a project
HomePrivacy policy
Privacy policy
PATH recognizes and respects the privacy of our online visitors. PATH only collects personal information that website visitors choose to share with us when signing up to receive e-newsletters, making charitable contributions, or applying for jobs. Any information collected on this website is used solely by PATH for internal purposes. PATH does not sell contact lists or personal user information to third parties. In specific cases, PATH may share personally identifiable information with third parties when the person submitting the information actively authorizes us to share it or we are required to by law.
If you wish to review personal information we may have on file, request corrections to mail and email addresses, or change permissions regarding sharing information with third parties, please contact development [at] path.org (development [at] path.org(link sends e-mail)).
We care about the safety and security of your online donation. We use a secure encrypted donation service provided by Convio which can send and receive private information across the public Internet. Every credit card donation is encrypted using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) specification before it is sent from the individual's computer over the Internet.
